





linkedin.com/in/nickbravodev

# PERFORMANCE PROFILE

Designer and developer with proven teamwork and leadership experience. Successfully implemented projects by structuring project requirements efficiently. Produced effective print and digital assets and built converting websites, digital products, and frontends with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. Strong Proficiency in Figma and Visual Studio Code, master of Adobe XD, Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop.

# **HARD SKILLS**

- Graphic / Layout Design
- **Product Design**
- UI/UX Design
- Adohe XD
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe Photoshop
- Figma
- HTML / CSS / JavaScript

# SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Visual Content Creation
- **Decision Making**
- Team Leadership
- Strategic Planning
- Interpersonal Communication
- Critical Thinking
- Presentations

# **EXPERIENCE**

### WEB DEVELOPER

## **MAVERIK. 2023 - PRESENT**

· I'm building the new and improved Maverik.com. I work with the marketing team to produce landing pages and content that flows with active campaigns.

#### **DIRECTOR OF WEB DEVELOPMENT**

### **ASTROPOST. 2022 - PRESENT**

• I design, build, and maintain multiple high-performing and engaging websites, visual identities, and online assets to solidify brand authority and trust across platforms.

#### FREELANCE DESIGNER / DEVELOPER

#### FREELANCE. 2007 - 2022

· I designed and built engaging websites, user interfaces, visual identities, digital products, and online assets.

#### **GRAPHIC DESIGNER / WEB DEVELOPER**

#### 8FISH. 2008 - 2009

Elevated brands by designing brand identities, web and print graphics, websites, social media content, and other digital media assets.

#### POLICE OFFICER

#### POLICE DEPARTMENT, 2021 - 2023

· Contributed to educational and community outreach campaigns as the liaison between the police department and the marketing department.

#### POLICE DETECTIVE

### POLICE DEPARTMENT. 2015 - 2021

· Developed and supervised a comprehensive firearm deployment and training program and impacted lives through empathetic communication and complete criminal investigations.

### POLICE LIEUTENANT

## POLICE DEPARTMENT. 2010 - 2015

- Improved transparency and community relationships by building the department's first website and social media channels and providing timely press releases.
- Developed Reserve Officer program that slashed personnel budget by 30%.

# **EDUCATION**

**BACHELOR OF SCIENCE / DIGITAL CINEMATOGRAPHY** 

UNIVERSITY **GPA 3.99 / VALEDICTORIAN** 

**ASSOCIATE OF APPLIED SCIENCE / GRAPHIC DESIGN** 

COLLEGE OF